Didn't you say to call you
when I found a USB?
There's someone here,
a message for Andrew.
I know who got it, it's Panot!
He said someone wanted
to buy it.
Well then, I'll buy it.
Be careful when you go to Panot.
The woman at the market
is here again.
It looks like she's looking
for something.
Hurry up! Go there!
Okay, Madam.
Where can I find that Panot?
This is the factory they're
talking about in Purok Tres.
You still can't find the woman?
But we have an update, Madam.
There's an addict at the market.
He's selling a USB
with a video of the deceased
Police Officer Bolagos.
I'll deal with them myself.
Miguel, is there anyone outside
helping you?
I'll tell you when I'm sure.
Don't you trust me anymore,
Buddy?
They're buying the USB
from the gang of addicts.
Give me the flash drive.
You don't want it.
Gotcha!
You guys are crazy!
The deal earlier was clear?
- Give it to me.
- Damn you!
It's time to meet that freakin'
girl and get that video.
What's that?
You even brought a backup!
The video...
I found you, Theresa Park.
Joey, let's go!
The flash drive.
No, don't.
Joey, don't!
Joey!
So it's you.
Well, I wanted to meet you.
But this will do.
Joey, this way!
Madam, you are hit.
Come on, let's get Madam
out of here!
Let's go.
Get down! Get down!
Hey!
You?
What are you doing here?
Do you know him?
No.
Now is not the time for talking.
Just stay here, okay?
You...
Can you protect them?
I got to go.
Wait! Just don't leave!
Come back...
Stop!
Jin Ho?
I got you now.
What are you waiting for?
Shoot him!
No more shooting.
Maybe they're all dead.
That's why let's leave now.
Get in the car.
Why?
You're not out of danger.
They might stay around
to follow you.
You can't go home now.
My car is also far away.
If they catch us on a motorbike,
we don't stand a chance either.
You want them to find you here,
or are we going?
Let's go.
Beauty!
Come in.
So...
You're safe here.
Who are you really,
and why are you always
showing up?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry?
You should learn our language.
You're in our country.
And not that I'm the one
who gets nosebleeds
because of you before
we understand each other.
How did you meet him?
That's my stalker.
He's the one who saved me
at the market.
Stalker?
Hey, I'm your savior.
I saved your life twice!
But why are you always near her
when she gets in trouble?
Because he's a stalker.
Hey!
No need for violence, okay.
I'll explain everything.
And no...
No pepper spray,
please.
Calm down, okay?
So my name is Jin Ho,
Lee Jin Ho.
I am from the National
Intelligence Service in Korea.
Yes,
I'm an agent.
So,
I'm looking for a crime boss
from Korea.
And I need to bring her back
to our country.
Recently, she's hiding here
in the Philippines.
She changed her name,
even her face.
Why are you following me?
Do I look like a crime boss
to you?
I'm just a student.
The woman in the video.
The one you posted
on the internet.
It's Theresa Park.
That's the one I'm looking for.
You're lucky it's just
a graze wound.
That was supposed
to be an easy job!
I was about to kill that...
but then Jin ho ruined
everything!
You'll be in trouble when
Berdugo finds out about this.
Loloy can now clean the site.
That's the least of my concerns.
My problem now, aside from that
freakin' video, is Jin Ho!
He found me!
Stop!
Jin ho?
I got you now.
He recognized me! He saw me!
That Jin Ho won't stop
bothering me!
This is how I found you.
You posted the video using
an anonymous account,
but it's not that hard to track.
So this Theresa Park
that you're talking about
is an international crime boss?
What's her business?
Drugs?
Yes.
That Theresa Park,
that's the one who killed
Ramon Orbos, not Father.
We already have proof now.
How can we help Father?
Let's go. Let's check the stuff
in the shop.
Hey, stop!
You're not going anywhere.
What?
To be honest,
I don't know the person
I married anymore.
Well, then, don't come back
here.
I don't need your pity.
It's Mother.
No phone.
Clarissa.
I thought you left already.
I can't leave you alone.
I'm worried about you.
I brought you some food.
Have you eaten yet?
Why do you seem worried?
Is there a problem, Clarissa?
Why?
Joey isn't answering my calls.
What's with you?
Give me my phone.
Give me my phone!
Give me that back!
Ouch!
Won't you help?
Don't you have a gun?
Joey, let's listen to him first.
Aren't you curious
about what he is saying?
What if it's connected
to your father's case?
What are you saying?
Fine!
Let Peter go first,
then I'll listen to you!
We have to feel safe first!
Listen.
This is the safest place
for you now.
If you leave,
those men will come after you.
They will follow you
to your house, to your family...
And they will kill you.
So please stay here
until I get Theresa.
Then you'll be safe.
I'll make sure of it.
I promise.
Fine.
We will stay.
What?
Joey, he's right.
After what happened to us
earlier,
we're not sure if Theresa is
following us or waiting for us.
So yeah,
we'll be staying here for the
night since we're all exhausted.
But tomorrow, we'll figure out
what to do with Theresa.
Maybe the kid is just busy.
I'm nervous too, Diego.
Wait.
What?
Okay, we'll stay.
I just need to talk
to my Mother first.
Do not tell her your situation.
This remains confidential
until it's over.
Hello, Mother?
Joey, why aren't you answering
your phone?
Are you still out?
What time is it?
I'm just at the boarding house.
I've got a lot of work
to do with my project.
Have you visited Father yet?
Your Godfather Diego
went to see him.
He said your father is okay.
Joey, your mother is worried
about you.
How are you? Are you okay?
Godfather...
Finish it.
Godfather, okay, next time,
okay?
I still have a lot to do.
Mother, I love you.
Love you, Joey! Call me, okay?
Happy?
You don't have to be mad at me.
I'm doing this for your sake.
Okay.
We are all tired.
Let's just rest.
So, you can have this room.
I'll sleep on the couch.
What? So you can watch over us?
So we can't escape, right?
Maybe you want to take
our cell phones.
Yes, give me your cell phones.
No way!
Give it to him.
Can't you be apart from your
cell phones for even one night?
Go ahead.
Give me.
Phone.
You.
So everybody, listen.
You can't call anyone tonight.
Don't worry.
I keep the big ones.
I can't trust all of you.
But with you, we can trust you,
is that it?
Your gun.
My gun?
Yes.
Here.
I'll bring you what you need.
Just wait for me.
Andrew!
Why did you give him your gun?
Now we don't stand a chance
against him.
Joey, if he wanted to kill us,
he would have done it
a while ago.
And you said he saved you twice.
So you two, stop complaining
so much.
You're whining a lot.
I really don't trust
that Andrew.
I think he wouldn't sleep in
someone's house, would he?
You know, let him go.
Just get some rest.
I won't sleep.
I'll watch over you.
Hey.
What are you doing there?
Why are you here?
Isn't it time for you to go
to bed?
I knew it.
I knew it! You're just lying
about trusting Jin Ho.
What are you looking for there?
Can't you just not talk?
You're the one who got us
involved here.
That's why you don't want us
to leave
because you want to include this
in your story too.
What if something happens
to Peter and me?
Is there anything you can do?
Just don't make a noise.
What are you doing there?
What are you doing?
Get up.
Step away from my things.
Please don't kill us.
It's his fault!
Yes.
Well, she's right.
Keep her out of this.
This is between you and me.
So you want us to stay
because you want to put your
story on your vlog.
Isn't that what you did
to my Father?
And now, you're going to do it
to us?
You're good at getting other
people into trouble.
Can you fix the flash drive?
Did you ask your people
if they saw the flash drive?
It contains a video
of Ramon and me.
Godfather, can we meet?
About the evidence I'm saying
will help Father.
You're still in danger.
I'm here to protect you.
Maybe that policeman can still
perform a miracle.
Why don't we just kill him?
I think that Parak holds
a position.
This is it!
Joey, I'd like to introduce you
to someone!
You?
His name is Jin Ho!